cryptopros.biz 2019-06-01

# Crypto Pros » Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience

_Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs._

To improve our website

_We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you._

To process transactions

_Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested._

To send periodic emails

_The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc._

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**  

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**  

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and Affiliates. If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us via the Crypto Pro support page.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other’s rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. Members and advertisers also display third party content and links as included with purchased services on our website. 

These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nevertheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Your Consent**  

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
